potguide.com 2019-04-07

# Privacy Policy | PotGuide.com

## PGED Corp.  
Privacy Policy

Date of last revision: June 14th, 2018

## Who We Are?

The name of our company is PGED Corp., also known as PotGuide, and we’re a company located in Colorado that’s a resource for the cannabis industry. Our site consists of business directories, deals systems, events systems, strain profiles and product reviews. The site also contains booking functionality for lodging and activities.

## What Is This?

This is a privacy policy and the reason we have it is to tell you how we collect, manage, store, and use your information.

Just so we’re clear, whenever we say “we,” “us,” “our,” or “ourselves”, we’re talking about PGED Corp. and whenever we say “you” or “your,” we’re talking about the person or business who has decided to use our services. And since we do a lot of different stuff, when we talk about our services, we mean any of our websites or apps; or any features, products, graphics, text, images, photos, audio, video, or similar things we use.

## Why Are We Showing You This?

We value and respect your privacy. That is why we strive to only use your information when we think that doing so improves your experience in using our services. If you feel that we could improve in this mission in any way, or if you have a complaint or concern, please let us know by sending us your feedback to the following email address: [privacy@potguide.com](mailto:privacy@potguide.com).

Our goal is to be as transparent and open about our use of information and data as possible, so that our users can benefit from both the way they provide information and how we use it.

This privacy policy should be read along with our Terms of Service, posted at https://potguide.com/terms-of-service/ That’s another big part of what we do, so please review it and follow its process for questions or concerns about what it says there.

## Information Collection and Use

In using the services, you may be asked to provide us a variety of information– some of which can personally identify you and some that cannot. We may collect, store, and share this personal information with third parties, but only in the ways we explain in this policy. Here’s how we do it and why we do it:

  1. ### Personally Identifiable Information: How we collect it.

Personally identifiable information is data that can be used to contact or identify a single person. Examples include your name, you phone number, your email, your address, and your IP address. We collect this kind of information in the following ways:

    * Information you give us when you create an account with us: This information includes your name, your email address, and your password hash.
    * Information we obtain when you join our email list: This is just your email.
    * Information for giveaways and competitions: This is usually your name, email, and date of birth.
    * We collect cookies to maintain session information on our sites.
    * We use Google Analytics, and this also sets cookies. We have the demographic feature of Google Analytics active.
    * We use the Google Maps API, please reference the [Google Privacy Policy.](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy)
  2. ### Personally Identifiable Information: How we use it.

PGED Corp. uses your information in the following ways:

    * Our email list allows us to contact you by email.
    * Your account information is used to assist with user login functionality to leave reviews, “like” deals, and to view your travel itinerary.
    * The giveaway information is used to enroll you in contests and promotions, and to select and notify winners.
    * All of the information we receive is used to tailor our services to your needs and the way you use our services.
    * We collect cookies to maintain session information on our sites.
    * We use Google Analytics, and this also sets cookies. We have the demographic feature of Google Analytics active.
  3. ### Who We Share Your Information With and Why

PGED Corp. only shares your information with third parties in the following ways and for the following purposes:

    1. We will share any information provided for activity and lodging bookings with our software as a service providers to facilitate those bookings and to complete the transactions.
    2. We share your giveaway information with contest sponsors to assist with their promotions and as an incentive for the contests sponsors to give contests.
    3. We share your information with Hubspot to help us better segment/target our user base with quality content.
    4. We will share all collected information to the extent necessary and as required by law or to comply with any legal obligations, including defense of our company.
  4. ### Information We Get From Other Places

We also receive information from other sources, such as Expedia, FareHarbor, Peek, and Checkfront. For Expedia bookings, we collect your first/last name, address, email, phone, and credit-card information. From FareHarbor, Peek, and Checkfront, we also receive your names, addresses, email, phone, and credit-card information. We do not store information specific to your credit card (that is, your credit card number, date, or security code), or your activity data as it pertains to those platforms. We store information from Expedia bookings for 3 years.

We also receive information from Google Analytics, Facebook log in, and your Google log in.

We receive all of this information consistent with those companies’ privacy policies. For information about their privacy policies, please visit those sites.

  5. ### Your Choices in What Information You Share

We do not require you to provide any personal data to visit the site, including to view our directories, deals system, blog content, etc. Our process for collecting information begins when you create an account, sign up for a promotion, or register for an activity. We will request your consent to use your data at that time. We will not use your data for more than the purpose for which it was collected.

  6. ### Non-Personally Identifiable Information

Non-personally identifiable information includes general details about your device and connection (including the type of computer/mobile device, operating system, web-browser or other software, language preference, and hardware); general information from the app store or referring website; the date and time of visit or use; and, internet content provider information. We may collect your non-personally identifying information when you visit our site by accessing Google Analytics, through software that collects and stores this information or other means.

  7. ### How Long We Keep Your Information

Unless otherwise specified, we will retain your Personally identifiable information for as long as you use our services, or until you request in writing that we delete or otherwise remove your Personally identifiable information.

Google Analytics information is stored for 38 months then deleted.

Expedia Lodgings information is stored for 3 years then deleted.

Furthermore, when we process information, we retain a record, to the extent reasonably possible, of the following information: the processor, purpose of the processing, categories of individuals and data involved, nature of disclosure, if there is a transfer of information over national boundaries, the length of time the information will be held before erasure, and the security measures involved.

  8. ### Where We Keep and Transfer Your Information

Our business is operated in the United States and third parties with whom we share your information are as well. Our servers are located here and this is where your data and information will be stored.

Please be aware if you are a citizen of another country, and if you live in Europe in particular, that your information will be transferred out of your home country and into the United States. The United States might not have the same level of data protection as your country provides.

Based outside of the EU, we do not focus our business in the EU. We do not directly solicit privacy data from those located in the EU, but to the extent that we occasionally process personal data from individuals in the EU, we do not do so in a way that is targeted to reveal race; ethnicity; political, religious, or philosophical beliefs; trade union memberships; health; sexual activity; or, sexual orientation.

If you would like more information about this, please email us at [privacy@potguide.com](mailto:privacy@potguide.com).

  9. ### EU Rights to Information

According to the laws of the European Union (except for limited exceptions, where applicable), anyone in those countries has the right to:

    * Be informed about their data and its processing
    * Have access to their data
    * Correct any errors in their data
    * Erase data from our records
    * Restrict processing and use of data
    * Data portability
    * Object to the use of their data, including for the purpose of automated profiling and direct marketing
    * Make decisions about automated decision making and profiling

PGED Corp. respects each of these rights for all of its users, regardless of citizenship. If you have any questions or concerns about any of these rights, or if you would like to assert any of these rights at any time, please contact [privacy@potguide.com](mailto:privacy@potguide.com). Before we use your information in any way not authorized in this privacy policy, we will contact you to request your informed consent.

## Protecting Your Information

  1. ### Keeping it Safe

PGED Corp. makes reasonable and commercially feasible efforts to keep your information safe. Though we are a small business, we have appropriate security measures in place to prevent your information from being accidentally lost, used, or accessed in an unauthorized way. We restrict access to your personal information to those who need to know it, are subject to contractual confidentiality obligations, and may be disciplined or terminated if they fail to meet these obligations. Those processing your information will do so only in an authorized manner and are subject to a duty of confidentiality.

We also:

    * Encrypt many of our services using SSL
    * We are PCI compliant
    * We do monthly PCI scans
    * We do server patches every 30 days
    * We regularly review our processes to consider if there are any additional improvements we can make to our systems.

That said, no organization or business can guarantee 100% data protection. With that in mind, we also have procedures in place to deal with any suspected data security breach. We will inform both you and any applicable authorities of a suspected data security breach, as and when required by law.

  2. ### Links to Other Websites

Our site has links to the sites, content, and services of other businesses, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, and other third parties. Any products or services found through a link to any of these other sites are subject to separate privacy policies. PGED Corp. is not liable for any content provided or actions taken by such third parties.

  3. ### Posting Content to Our Site or Social Media

Any content you post on this site or others, including through social media links, is likely to become publicly available and may not be fully revocable or erasable by PGED Corp., because it will have become available to third parties. You can always ask us to delete information in our possession, but we cannot force anyone else to erase your information. Please be aware that you publish such information at your own risk.

  4. ### Do Not Track Signals

Some technologies, such as web browsers or mobile devices, provide a setting that when turned on sends a Do Not Track (DNT) signal when browsing a website or app. There is currently no common standard for responding to DNT Signals or even in the DNT signal itself. We currently do not have any technology implemented to process DNT Signals.

  5. ### Use by Minors Expressly Prohibited

This website, its content, and our services are not intended for anyone under the age of 21. PGED Corp. does not knowingly collect information from those under the age of 21. PGED Corp. learns it has accidentally collected such information, it will be deleted.

  6. ### Compliance with Regulators

We regularly review our privacy policy to do our best to ensure it complies with any applicable laws. Ours is a small business, but when we receive formal written complaints, we will contact the person who made the complaint to follow up as soon as practicable. We will work with relevant regulatory authorities to resolve any complaints or concerns that we cannot resolve with our users directly.

You also have the right to file a complaint with the supervisory authority of your home country, where available, relating to the processing of any personal data you feel may have violated local regulations.

## General Information for Your Further Understanding

  1. ### No Unsolicited Personal Information Requests

We will never ask you for your personal information in an unsolicited letter, call, or email. If you contact us, we will only use your personal information if necessary to fulfill your request.

  2. ### Changes

Our business and the services we provide are constantly evolving. We may change our privacy policy at any time. If we change our policy, we will affirmatively request that you consent to the new policy or email you for consent at that time. We will not reduce your rights under this policy without your consent.

  3. ### Security

The security of our services is important to us. We use reasonable efforts to secure any information you provide to our systems. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, we cannot guarantee your security. As with disclosure of any information electronically, there is a risk that any information you disclose by use of the services could be collected or used by others. This could result in unsolicited messages from third parties or use of such information by third parties for their own purposes, legal or illegal. You hereby waive any claims against us and agree not to hold us liable for the theft or misuse of personal information.

  4. ### Complaints

PGED Corp. respects the rights of all of its users, regardless of location or citizenship. If you have any questions or concerns about any of these rights, or if you would like to assert any of these rights at any time, please contact [privacy@potguide.com](mailto:privacy@potguide.com).

  5. ### Questions about Policy

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, contact us at: [privacy@potguide.com](mailto:privacy@potguide.com). By accessing any of our services or content, you are affirming that you understand and agree with the terms of our Privacy Policy.
